Contact

amking15@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-king-b0035a136 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Analytical Skills
Problem Solving
Teamwork

Languages

English

Certifications

CREATE A SUBNET

Open Systems Interconnection model (OSI model)

Anthony King

Senior Application Support Analyst at RELEX Solutions Atlanta, Georgia

Summary

Highly skilled Application Support Analyst with working knowledge in Unix and Linux-based systems. Vast experience in high-volume environments with strong analytical communication and organizational abilities. Complex problem solver able to thrive in fast-paced and challenging roles.

Experience

RELEX Solutions
Senior Application Support Analyst
January 2019 - Present
Greater Atlanta Area

RELEX Solutions
Application Support Analyst
June 2017 - Present
Greater Atlanta Area

- Specifically providing technical solutions for our customers from Europe and the United States pertaining to the RELEX Software and Hardware Infrastructures. My daily job tasks involve, but are not confined to:
- Remote Deployment of Test and Production Environment for new and existing clients (Capistrano Deploy via Deploy Server or Deployment tool via Mordor)
- Investigate error messages and bugs within UI, as well as error messages with optimization runs within UI (java logs, ruby logs, server logs(production, processor, gc activity logs)
- Handling Application Support Requests (critical file search via servers, data retrieval, troubleshooting, etc), diagnose and resolve in a timely manner.
- Monitoring Software and Hardware Infrastructure. Eg: Server disk space and memory maintenance .
- Use monitoring tools (Grafana and Zabbix) that collects data from servers, virtual machines that create graphs so you can analyze it for trends or problems.
- Investigate slow performance issues within UI

Page 1 of 3

- Deploy RELEX Software Version Updates
- Transfer environments between servers to perform maintenance or for better performance.
- Refresh test environments database from production environments or vice versa (copying database from origin and transferring it to target environment)
- Request missing data files from the client, to make sure they get their scheduled Order Proposal on time.
- Provide great communication skills to customers via email
- Display working knowledge with Unix/Linux command line

Vonage Business Technical Support Representative May 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Greater Atlanta Area

- Primary responsibilities include analyzing and utilizing SIP Protocols to configure client Routers, VoIP phone systems and PBX Server
- Answered any Tier 2 requests for network and phone support via email or inbound or outbound calls
- Provide customer-focused support using clear and descriptive methods
- Handle calls varying from phone setup to in-depth network analysis
- Maintain working knowledge of Cisco, Panasonic, Yealink, Grand stream, Polycom, and other VoIP phones
- Manage and document customer care cases via Salesforce CRM
- Research and resolved customer focused technical issues in a timely manner
- Track case tickets within a Customer Relations Management System to Document resolutions for future reference both internally and externally

Robert Half Technology Install Technician (Contract) November 2016 - November 2016 (1 month)

Greater Atlanta Area

- Performed installations of adding an additional 4 GB of RAM memory to a large scale of Dell OptiPlex 9030 All-In-One (AIO) PCs at varies Home Depot sites
- Making the new total amount changing from 4 GB to 8 GB
- After installing memory and rebuilding back the PC, reimaging each PC to remove all software on PCs and reinstalling everything back to POS standards.

TEKsystems
Install Technician (Contract)
April 2016 - May 2016 (2 months)

Greater Atlanta Area

- Provide support to the Toshiba Team Lead in the performance of a large scale Point of Sale (POS) equipment refresh at varies Wal-Mart sites.
- Survey of Debit devices per instructions provided
- De-installation of existing POS equipment
- Installation of new POS equipment To include unboxing of new equipment
- POS equipment may include various peripheral components that differ from site to site
- Complete setup and initialization of equipment per instructions
- Register System Unit Replacement (RSUR) that is made up of the following:
- Cashier screen (some sites have multiple screens), receipt printer, keyboard, handheld scanner, flatbed scanner/scale, debit terminal (PinPad), cash drawer and customer screen

Education

Savannah State University

Bachelor's in Computer Science Technology, Computer Science · (2015)